<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sappy Secrets</string>

    <string name="title_activity_run_map">Sappy Mappy</string>
    <string name="settings_header">Set Pace</string>
    <string name="pace_setting_text">Select a pace for the mission.\nMission Duration:\n10–20 minutes</string>
    <string name="pace_set_button_text">Confirm Pace:\n%d minute mile</string>
    <string name="foreground_service_notification_title">Sappy Secrets GPS Tracker</string>
    <string name="foreground_service_notification_description">Tracking location for Sappy Secrets…</string>

    <string name="AI_runner_spokenName">AI runner</string>
    <string name="player_spokenName">player</string>

    <string name="interaction_injured">You are poisoned by Hemlock, so you can\'t do that. Go back to HQ to get better.</string>
    <string name="interaction_nothing_to_interact">Nothing here that can be interacted with.</string>

    <string name="headquarters_spokenName">your Shady Grove</string>
    <string name="headquarters_mapName">HQ</string>
    <string name="headquarters_build_not_enough_resources">It seems we need %d Vine Cred to set up the Shady Grove. Walk or jog around the neighborhood to get Vine Cred. You will hear this sound when you collect a Vine Cred.</string>
    <string name="headquarters_build">You built a Shady Grove, your first sappy sleuthing headquarters.</string>
    <string name="headquarters_fixInjuries">You cured your poison at the HQ. Now you feel as spry as a Sequoia!</string>
    <string name="headquarters_upgradeNotEnoughResources">You don\'t have the %d Intel required to upgrade your HQ.</string>
    <string name="headquarters_chase_message">Catch that agent!</string>
    <string name="headquarters_chaseStarted">You found the double agent! Chase it!</string>
    <string name="headquarters_chaseFailed">The double agent got away. Maybe we can find it again?</string>
    <string name="headquarters_chaseSuccess">You did it!</string>

    <string name="buildingresourcesite_spokenName">a Seedy Sapling</string>
    <string name="buildingresourcesite_mapName">Sapling</string>
    <string name="buildingresourcesite_spokenNameWithResources">%s with %d Secrets ready for you</string>
    <string name="buildingresourcesite_upgradeSuccess">You persuaded the Seedy Sapling to be your informant for %d Vine Cred.</string>
    <string name="buildingresourcesite_upgradeNotEnoughResources">You need at least %d Vine Cred to make this sapling your informant.</string>
    <string name="buildingresourcesite_collectSuccess">You sleuthed %d Secrets from the Sapling.</string>
    <string name="buildingresourcesite_collectOutOfResource">This Seedy Sapling is stumped for now. Come back later.</string>

    <string name="buildingsubresourcesite_spokenName">an Analyst Aspen with no leads</string>
    <string name="buildingsubresourcesite_spokenNameBuilt">an Analyst Aspen working on your lead</string>
    <string name="buildingsubresourcesite_mapName">Aspen</string>
    <string name="buildingsubresourcesite_upgradeSuccess">The Analyst Aspen found its first lead to analyze for your %d Vine Cred and %d Secrets.</string>
    <string name="buildingsubresourcesite_upgradeNotEnoughResources">You need at least %d Vine Cred and %d Secrets to get the Aspen its first lead.</string>
    <string name="buildingsubresourcesite_collectSuccess">After analyzing your %d Secrets, the Aspen gives you %d Intel.</string>
    <string name="buildingsubresourcesite_collectNotEnoughResources">You need %d Secrets for the Aspen to analyze for Intel.</string>
    <string name="buildingsubresourcesite_buildExpired">One of your Analyst Aspens lost their lead after too long with no new Secrets.</string>

    <string name="chasesite_spokenName">a Hemlock Haven</string>
    <string name="chasesite_mapName">Hemlock</string>
    <string name="chasesite_chaseStarted">A Hemlock begins chasing you! Run away! Quick!</string>
    <string name="chasesite_chaseSuccess">You outran the Hemlock. Whew! Good work.</string>
    <string name="chasesite_chaseFailed">The Hemlock caught you and poisoned you. Go back to HQ to get better.</string>
    <string name="chasesite_chaseMessage">The Hemlock is chasing you, run fast!</string>

    <string name="receivedMovementResource">You got more Vine Cred!</string>
    <string name="receivedMovementResource_short">Vine Cred!</string>
    <string name="discoveredNotification">You have discovered %s!</string>
    <string name="movementResourceAnnounce">You have %d Vine Cred</string>
    <string name="movementResourceAnnounceNone">You have no Vine Cred</string>
    <string name="buildingResourceAnnounce"> %d Secrets</string>
    <string name="buildingSubResourceAnnounce"> %d Intel</string>
    <string name="approachingAnnounce">You arrived at %s.</string>

    <string name="game_started">Hello Agent Almond. I\'m a complex artificially intelligent holographic lifeform. But you can call me Holly for short.</string>
    <string name="tutorialFirstResource">To build the Shady Grove, our first headquarters, press play somewhere.</string>
    <string name="tutorialHQbuilt_notEnoughResources">Keep collecting Vine Cred for the Shady Grove.</string>
    <string name="tutorialHQbuilt_readyToBuild">You have enough Vine Cred for your first headquarters, the Shady Grove. Choose a central location to build your headquarters and press play to build it.</string>
    <string name="tutorialResourceBuildingDiscovered">Now that we\'ve grown our Shady Grove, let\'s go investigate the area. Try pressing play to interact with every site you discover.</string>
    <string name="tutorialResourceBuildingUpgraded">Nice work finding a Seedy Sapling. Can we turn it to our side?</string>
    <string name="tutorialResourceBuildingCollected">I\'m glad that Seedy Sapling is working for us now.</string>
    <string name="tutorialSubResourceBuildingCollected">Now we have Secrets, but we need to find a way to understand them.</string>
    <string name="tutorialCompleted">I\'m picking up strange signals from HQ. Take that Intel back to the Shady Grove and upgrade it!</string>
    <string name="tutorialplayerinjured">You\'ve been poisoned. Go back to HQ for antidote.</string>

    <string name="list_separator">, </string>
    <string name="list_final_and">and </string>

    <string name="win_message">Nice work, Agent Almond! This looks like a Dogwood double agent. We need to find out what this means for the Oaken Empire. I\'ll send the debriefing to your mobile device.</string>

    <string name="text_medals">%dx Magnolia Medals</string>

    <string name="mission_1_briefing">As Agent Almond, a new recruit of the Oaken Empire, you ensure any arborous threats to the Empire are well-researched and that seedy schemes never blossom.\nThere are rumors of a double agent in the Tangle Woods. Your first mission is to plant a headquarters there and root out the opposing spy.</string>
    <string name="mission_1_debriefing">You managed to catch the double agent. The agent is part of a crop of rogues named the Dogwood Derelicts. We need to figure out why this treacherous tree was spying on the Oaken Empire and strip the bark off this conspiracy. But first, you deserve your reward.   -Holly</string>

    <string name="run_stats_contents">Mission Duration: %d:%02d\nAverage Pace: %d:%02d/mile\nDistance: %3.2f miles</string>

    <string name="feedback_email">feedback@sappysecrets.com</string>

    <string name="magnolia_medals_key">magnolia_medals</string>
    <string name="saved_pace_key">saved_pace</string>
    <string name="eula_agreed_key">EULA_AGREED</string>

    <string name="eula_title">End User License Agreement</string>
    <string name="accept">I Accept</string>
    <string name="decline">Decline</string>
    <string name="eula_content">This End User License Agreement (“Agreement”) is a binding agreement between you (“End User” or “you”) and Jamie Earl Studios, LLC, a Massachusetts limited liability company (“Company”). This Agreement governs your use of the Sappy Secrets application on Android, (including all related documentation, the “Application”). The Application is licensed, not sold, to you.
BY CLICKING THE “AGREE” BUTTON AND/OR USING THE APPLICATION, YOU (A) ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND THIS AGREEMENT; (B) REPRESENT THAT YOU ARE OF LEGAL AGE TO ENTER INTO A BINDING AGREEMENT; AND © ACCEPT THIS AGREEMENT AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE LEGALLY BOUND BY ITS TERMS. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, DO NOT USE THE APPLICATION AND DELETE IT FROM YOUR MOBILE DEVICE.
1.	License Grant. Subject to the terms of this Agreement, Company grants you a limited, non-exclusive, and nontransferable license to:
(a)	 download, install, and use the Application for your personal, non-commercial use on a single mobile device owned or otherwise controlled by you (“Mobile Device”) strictly in accordance with the Application\'s documentation; and
(b)	access, stream, download, and use on such Mobile Device the Content and Services (as defined in Section 5) made available in or otherwise accessible through the Application, strictly in accordance with this Agreement and the Terms of Use applicable to such Content and Services as set forth in Section 5.
2.	License Restrictions. Licensee shall not:
(a)	copy the Application, except as expressly permitted by this license;
(b)	modify, translate, adapt, or otherwise create derivative works or improvements, whether or not patentable, of the Application;
©	reverse engineer, disassemble, decompile, decode, or otherwise attempt to derive or gain access to the source code of the Application or any part thereof;
(d)	remove, delete, alter, or obscure any trademarks or any copyright, trademark, patent, or other intellectual property or proprietary rights notices from the Application, including any copy thereof;
(e)	rent, lease, lend, sell, sublicense, assign, distribute, publish, transfer, or otherwise make available the Application, or any features or functionality of the Application, to any third party for any reason, including by making the Application available on a network where it is capable of being accessed by more than one device at any time; or
(f)	remove, disable, circumvent, or otherwise create or implement any workaround to any copy protection, rights management, or security features in or protecting the Application.
3.	Safety. You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for using the Application in a safe and appropriate manner. Accordingly, you will maintain awareness of your surroundings, and play safely and in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. To the extent the Application permits you to post any content, you will not post any unlawful, inappropriate, inaccurate, misleading, or commercial content. Moreover, you will not harass, threaten, or otherwise violate the legal rights of any third party, and in furtherance of the foregoing, you will not trespass, or engage or encourage any activity that may result in injury, death, property damage, nuisance, or liability of any kind.
4.	Reservation of Rights. You acknowledge and agree that the Application is provided under license, and not sold, to you. You do not acquire any ownership interest in the Application under this Agreement, or any other rights thereto other than to use the Application in accordance with the license granted, and subject to all terms, conditions, and restrictions, under this Agreement. Company reserves and shall retain its entire right, title, and interest in and to the Application, including all copyrights, trademarks, and other intellectual property rights therein or relating thereto, except as expressly granted to you in this Agreement.
5.	Collection and Use of Your Information. You acknowledge that when you download, install, or use the Application, Company may use automatic means (including, for example, cookies and web beacons) to collect information about your Mobile Device and about your use of the Application. You also may be required to provide certain information about yourself as a condition to downloading, installing, or using the Application or certain of its features or functionality, and the Application may provide you with opportunities to share information about yourself with others. All information we collect through or in connection with this Application is subject to our Privacy Policy at https://sappysecrets.com/privacy/. By downloading, installing, using, and providing information to or through this Application, you consent to all actions taken by us with respect to your information in compliance with the Privacy Policy.
6.	Feedback. Company may collect your comments, suggestions, and feedback on the App, all of which shall be the exclusive property of Company.
7.	Content and Services. The Application may provide you with access to certain features, functionality, and content (collectively, “Content and Services”).
8.	Geographic Restrictions. The Content and Services are based in the Commonwealth of Massachusetts in the United States and provided for access and use only by persons located in the United States. You acknowledge that you may not be able to access all or some of the Content and Services outside of the United States and that access thereto may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access the Content and Services from outside the United States, you are responsible for compliance with local laws.
9.	Updates. Company may from time to time in its sole discretion develop and provide Application updates, which may include upgrades, bug fixes, patches, other error corrections, and/or new features (collectively, including related documentation, “Updates”). Updates may also modify or delete in their entirety certain features and functionality. You agree that Company has no obligation to provide any Updates or to continue to provide or enable any particular features or functionality. Based on your Mobile Device settings, when your Mobile Device is connected to the internet either:
(a)	the Application will automatically download and install all available Updates; or
(b)	you may receive notice of or be prompted to download and install available Updates.
You shall promptly download and install all Updates and acknowledge and agree that the Application or portions thereof may not properly operate should you fail to do so. You further agree that all Updates will be deemed part of the Application and be subject to all terms and conditions of this Agreement.
10.	Third-Party Materials. The Application may display, include, or make available third-party content (including data, information, applications, and other products, services, and/or materials) or provide links to third-party websites or services, including through third-party advertising (“Third-Party Materials”). You acknowledge and agree that Company is not responsible for Third-Party Materials, including their accuracy, completeness, timeliness, validity, copyright compliance, legality, decency, quality, or any other aspect thereof. Company does not assume and will not have any liability or responsibility to you or any other person or entity for any Third-Party Materials. Third-Party Materials and links thereto are provided solely as a convenience to you, and you access and use them entirely at your own risk and subject to such third parties\' terms and conditions.
11.	Term and Termination.
(a)	The term of Agreement commences when you download the Application and will continue in effect until terminated by you or Company as set forth in this Section 9.
(b)	You may terminate this Agreement by deleting the Application and all copies thereof from your Mobile Device.
©	Company may terminate this Agreement at any time without notice if it ceases to support the Application, which Company may do in its sole discretion. In addition, this Agreement will terminate immediately and automatically without any notice if you violate any of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
(d)	Upon termination:
(i)	all rights granted to you under this Agreement will also terminate; and
(ii)	you must cease all use of the Application and delete all copies of the Application from your Mobile Device and account.
(e)	Termination will not limit any of Company\'s rights or remedies at law or in equity.
12.	Disclaimer of Warranties. THE APPLICATION IS PROVIDED TO LICENSEE “AS IS” AND WITH ALL FAULTS AND DEFECTS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, COMPANY, ON ITS OWN BEHALF AND ON BEHALF OF ITS AFFILIATES AND ITS AND THEIR RESPECTIVE LICENSORS AND SERVICE PROVIDERS, EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED, STATUTORY, OR OTHERWISE, WITH RESPECT TO THE APPLICATION, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT, AND WARRANTIES THAT MAY ARISE OUT OF COURSE OF DEALING, COURSE OF PERFORMANCE, USAGE, OR TRADE PRACTICE. WITHOUT LIMITATION TO THE FOREGOING, COMPANY PROVIDES NO WARRANTY OR UNDERTAKING, AND MAKES NO REPRESENTATION OF ANY KIND THAT THE APPLICATION WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, ACHIEVE ANY INTENDED RESULTS, BE COMPATIBLE, OR WORK WITH ANY OTHER SOFTWARE, APPLICATIONS, SYSTEMS, OR SERVICES, OPERATE WITHOUT INTERRUPTION, MEET ANY PERFORMANCE OR RELIABILITY STANDARDS, OR BE ERROR-FREE, OR THAT ANY ERRORS OR DEFECTS CAN OR WILL BE CORRECTED.
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF OR LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATIONS ON THE APPLICABLE STATUTORY RIGHTS OF A CONSUMER, SO SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
13.	Limitation of Liability. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL COMPANY OR ITS AFFILIATES, OR ANY OF ITS OR THEIR RESPECTIVE LICENSORS OR SERVICE PROVIDERS, HAVE ANY LIABILITY ARISING FROM OR RELATED TO YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE APPLICATION OR THE CONTENT AND SERVICES FOR:
(a)	PERSONAL INJURY, PROPERTY DAMAGE, LOST PROFITS, COST OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF GOODWILL, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION, OR ANY OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, EXEMPLARY, SPECIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES.
(b)	DIRECT DAMAGES IN AMOUNTS THAT IN THE AGGREGATE EXCEED THE AMOUNT ACTUALLY PAID BY YOU FOR THE APPLICATION.
THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS WILL APPLY WHETHER SUCH DAMAGES ARISE OUT OF BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE AND REGARDLESS OF WHETHER SUCH DAMAGES WERE FORESEEABLE OR COMPANY WAS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW CERTAIN LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY SO SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
14.	Indemnification. You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Company and its officers, directors, employees, agents, affiliates, successors, and assigns from and against any and all losses, damages, liabilities, deficiencies, claims, actions, judgments, settlements, interest, awards, penalties, fines, costs, or expenses of whatever kind, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, arising from or relating to your use or misuse of the Application or your breach of this Agreement, including but not limited to the content you submit or make available through this Application.
15.	Export Regulation. The Application may be subject to US export control laws, including the US Export Administration Act and its associated regulations. You shall not, directly or indirectly, export, re-export, or release the Application to, or make the Application accessible from, any jurisdiction or country to which export, re-export, or release is prohibited by law, rule, or regulation. You shall comply with all applicable federal laws, regulations, and rules, and complete all required undertakings (including obtaining any necessary export license or other governmental approval), prior to exporting, re-exporting, releasing, or otherwise making the Application available outside the US.
16.	Dispute Resolution.
YOU AGREE THAT DISPUTES BETWEEN YOU AND COMPANY WILL BE RESOLVED BY BINDING, INDIVIDUAL ARBITRATION, AND YOU ARE WAIVING YOUR RIGHT TO A TRIAL BY JURY OR TO PARTICIPATE AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS ACTION OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING.
THIS NOTICE DOES NOT APPLY IF: (1) IF YOU ARE A RESIDENT OF ANY JURISDICTION WHICH DOES NOT ALLOW THIS ARBITRATION AGREEMENT, (2) IF YOU OPT OUT OF ARBITRATION AS DESCRIBED IN THE "ARBITRATION" SECTION BELOW, OR (3) EXCEPT FOR CERTAIN TYPES OF DISPUTES DESCRIBED IN SECTION ‎16(a), “ARBITRATION,” BELOW.
(a)	Arbitration. If you live in a jurisdiction that allows you to agree to arbitration, you and Company agree that any disputes will be settled by binding arbitration, except that each party retains the right: (i) to bring an individual action in small claims court, and (ii) to seek injunctive or other equitable relief in a court of competent jurisdiction to prevent the actual or threatened infringement, misappropriation, or violation of a party’s copyrights, trademarks, trade secrets, patents, or other intellectual property rights (the action described in this clause (ii), an “IP Protection Action”). Notwithstanding this arbitration agreement, Company reserves the right to bring an action in any court of competent jurisdiction against you to stop and/or seek compensation for the intentional or willful misuse or abuse (e.g. hacking or falsifying location) of its intellectual property, Content and Services.
(b)	Opt-Out. Without limiting the preceding paragraph, you will also have the right to litigate any other dispute if you provide Company with written notice of your desire to do so by email to arbitration@sappysecrets.com within thirty (30) days following the date you first accept these Terms (such notice, an “Arbitration Opt-out Notice”). If you don’t provide Company with an Arbitration Opt-out Notice within the thirty (30) day period, you will be deemed to have knowingly and intentionally waived your right to litigate any dispute except as expressly set forth in clauses (a)(i) and (ii) above. Further, unless both you and Company otherwise agree in writing, the arbitrator may not consolidate more than one person’s claims, and may not otherwise preside over any form of any class or representative proceeding. If this class action waiver is held unenforceable, then the parties’ agreement to arbitrate will be deemed void. Except as provided in the preceding sentence, this “Dispute Resolution” section will survive any termination of these Terms. If the terms of this Section ‎16 “Arbitration” are found unenforceable as to any claim for relief, that claim must be severed from the arbitration and brought pursuant to Section ‎18, “Governing Law and Exclusive Venue.” All other claims will be arbitrated. The arbitrator, and not any court or agency, shall have exclusive authority to (i) determine the scope and enforceability of this arbitration agreement and (ii) resolve any dispute related to its interpretation, applicability, enforceability, or formation including any claim that all or any part of it is void or voidable.
©	Arbitration Rules. The arbitration will be administered by the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”) in accordance with the Commercial Arbitration Rules and the Supplementary Procedures for Consumer-Related Disputes (the “AAA Rules”) then in effect, except as modified by this “Dispute Resolution” section.
(d)	Arbitration Process. A party who desires to initiate arbitration must provide the other party with a written Demand for Arbitration as specified in the AAA Rules. (The AAA provides a general Demand for Arbitration) The single arbitrator will be either a retired judge or an attorney licensed to practice law and will be selected by the parties from the AAA’s roster of arbitrators. If the parties are unable to agree upon an arbitrator within fourteen (14) days of delivery of the Demand for Arbitration, then the AAA will appoint the arbitrator in accordance with the AAA Rules.
(e)	Arbitration Location and Procedure. Unless you and Company otherwise agree, the arbitration will be conducted in a confidential manner, in the county where you reside. If your claim does not exceed $10,000, then the arbitration will be conducted solely on the basis of the documents that you and Company submit to the arbitrator, and there will be no other discovery conducted (such as depositions), unless the arbitrator determines that a hearing is necessary. If your claim exceeds $10,000, your right to a hearing will be determined by the AAA Rules. Subject to the AAA Rules, the arbitrator will have the discretion to direct a reasonable exchange of information by the parties, consistent with the expedited nature of the arbitration. Notwithstanding the arbitrator’s discretion, absent a showing of good cause, in no event shall the parties be allowed more than three (3) depositions per side, and there will be no corporate deposition of the type contemplated by Federal Rule of Civil Procedure 30(b)(6).
(f)	Arbitral Award. The arbitrator will render an award within the time frame specified in the AAA Rules. The arbitrator’s decision will be treated as confidential, and will include the essential findings and conclusions upon which the arbitrator based the award. Confirmation and enforcement of the arbitration award may be done in any court of competent jurisdiction. The arbitrator’s award of damages must be consistent with the terms of Section ‎13 “Limitation of Liability” as to the types and amounts of damages for which a party may be held liable. The arbitrator may award declaratory or injunctive relief only in favor of the claimant and only to the extent necessary to provide relief warranted by the claimant’s individual claim.
17.	Severability. If any provision of this Agreement is illegal or unenforceable under applicable law, the remainder of the provision will be amended to achieve as closely as possible the effect of the original term and all other provisions of this Agreement will continue in full force and effect.
18.	Governing Law and Exclusive Venue. To the extent that this Agreement allows you or Company to initiate litigation in a court, other than for small claims court actions, both you and Company agree to the exclusive jurisdiction of and venue in the state and federal courts located in Boston, Massachusetts. Each of the parties hereto waives any objection to jurisdiction and venue in such courts. These Terms and your use of the Services are governed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, excluding its conflicts-of-law rules. If you are resident in a jurisdiction in which this clause is prohibited by local law, this section does not apply to you, and does not deprive you of the protection of the mandatory provisions of the consumer protection laws in your country.
19.	Limitation of Time to File Claims. ANY CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM YOU MAY HAVE ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THIS AGREEMENT OR THE APPLICATION MUST BE COMMENCED WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES OTHERWISE SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM IS PERMANENTLY BARRED.
20.	Entire Agreement. This Agreement and our Privacy Policy constitute the entire agreement between you and Company with respect to the Application and supersede all prior or contemporaneous understandings and agreements, whether written or oral, with respect to the Application.
21.	Waiver. No failure to exercise, and no delay in exercising, on the part of either party, any right or any power hereunder shall operate as a waiver thereof, nor shall any single or partial exercise of any right or power hereunder preclude further exercise of that or any other right hereunder. In the event of a conflict between this Agreement and any applicable purchase or other terms, the terms of this Agreement shall govern.</string>
    <string name="feedback_email_content">Dear Sappy Secrets Developers,\n\n

    I play-tested your game and beat the first mission. You are so lucky to have me has a play-tester. Here is some of my feedback.\n\n

    The most frustrating thing was:\n\n

    I had the most fun when:\n\n

    I don\'t understand what was going on when:\n\n

    My strategy, if I did the mission again, would be to:\n\n

    The style and script made me feel:\n\n

    I was also thinking:\n\n

    It\'s OK/not OK to follow up with me for more feedback:\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="mission_aborted_story">You aborted the mission. Try again later!</string>
    <string name="rewards_contents_none">None</string>
    <string name="latest_mission_unlock_key">latest_mission_unlock</string>
    <string name="dropsite_spokenName">a Dogwood Dead Drop</string>
    <string name="dropsite_mapName">DDD</string>
    <string name="dropsite_fixInjuries">You fixed up your injuries at the Dogwood Dead Drop. You are spry as a sapling now!</string>
    <string name="gps_dialog_message">Getting an accurate lock on your location…\nGo outside under a clear sky.\nAccuracy: %3.2f meters</string>
</resources>
